------------------OP-----------------------------
------------------ED-----------------------------
何だこれ
酢の物ですか
私が味を見てみましょう
一宿の礼のつもりでしょうかね
樱律联萌站 http://bbs.ylbud.com/
樱律联萌站为您带来高质量中日双语字幕
中日双语字幕由 樱律字幕组 制作
感谢以下成员倾情制作
听译：五月、吉禾　校对：jez　时间轴：咲夜　后期：OMG
What is this?
"Pickled vegetables"...
どうだ
Perhaps she means to
thank us for letting her stay.
敵ながらなかなか
I will sample it, Sire.
床に鍵が落ちてるのはどう言うことでしょう
多分出る前に窓を開けといて
Well?
玄関の鍵を閉めたから
Quite good, for enemy food...
投げれだんだろう
Why is there a key on the floor?
さすがは勇者
品行方正なことで
I'd say she opened the window
before she locked the door outside,
お前だったらどうするんだ
決まっています
鍵をかけて
then tossed the key through it.
そのまま鍵を待ち帰ります
That's a hero for you. Exemplary conduct.
お前悪魔だ
悪魔ですが、何か
What would you do?
That's obvious.
I would lock the door,
then take the key with me.
You're a demon.
Indeed. And?
この瞬間
在这瞬间
この場所がスダート
这里就是起点
イメージして見よう
试着想象一下
何ができるのかな
我能做些什么
Kono shunkan, kono basho ga sutaato
信じられない出来事だってある
会发生些不可思议的事吧
Imeeji shite miyou nani ga dekiru no ka na
もっと超えて行けるね
克服一切走的更远
Shinjirarenai dekigoto datte aru
ゼロから生まれるすべて輝いて
从零重生的一切都特别耀眼
Motto... koete yukeru ne
FLYあの空へ
翱翔朝着那片天空
Zero kara umareru subete kagayaite ano sora e
思い切り羽ばたきたい
想尽情地展翅
最高のスマイルで笑いながら
以最完美的笑容
さぁ、行く
笑着前行吧
Omoikiri habatakitai
未知の世界へと　今飛び出そうよ
奔向未知的世界仿佛就要飞出来
Saikou no sumairu de warainagara saa yukou!
未来を選び決めるのは自分
自己决定自己的未来
Michi no sekai e to ima tobidasou yo
夢を追いかけて行　こう泣く日をある
追逐着梦想前进　也会有哭泣的日子
それは大事な願い消えないで
珍贵的愿望不会消失
Mirai wo erabi, kimeru no wa jibun
Yume wo oikakete yukou
きっと会えるから
一定可以再次遇
Naku hi mo aru
明日の君
朝着未来的你
Sore wa daiji na negai, kienaide
Kitto aeru kara, asu no kimi e...
"The Devil is a Part-Timer!"
I feel defiled.
磨けがされた思いだわ
The Devil Goes on a Date
with His Junior in Shinjuku
魔王、新宿で後輩とデートする
次のニュースです
Turning to our next story...
Shots were fired in a residential area
of Shibuya before dawn this morning.
昨夜見目渋谷区の住宅外で
銃撃事件が起きました
Several bullet marks have been
found in nearby buildings,
ビールにはいつから銃弾の跡が確認され
Gunfire in the City
No Casualties
and a bicycle hit with multiple
shots was abandoned near the scene.
まだ、現場付近には銃弾が打ち込まれた
自転車が放置されていました
- Gah, those two!
- Police believe it's related to the crime,
アイツら
- Idiots...
- Police believe it's related to the crime,
あの馬鹿
- Well, I guess it's not my problem.
- and are tracking down the owner now.
まあ、関係ないか
Police are investigating
possible links to a recent string
まだ、この現場付近では最近
深夜のコンビニごとや路上ごとが多発してより
of late-night muggings and convenience
store robberies in the neighborhood.
警察は、昨夜の銃撃事件との因果関係を調べています
- Oh dear, that's almost our neighborhood!
- Moving on...
あら、これ近所じゃない
- Isn't that right near where you work, honey?
- There was an earthquake in the Kanto region
あんたところのバイト先の近くじゃないの
at approximately 6:20 this morning.
関東地方で地震が発生しました
I'm not joking or imagining things.
I really think an earthquake is coming!
遊びや空想じゃないんです
本当に地震が起こりそうなんです
Um, if you don't mind, could I ask
your advice about this in person?
あの、もし平気だったら直接会って
相談に乗ってもらえませんか？
Here goes!
Okay. Does tomorrow evening work?
分かった。
明日の夕方でいいか？
I've got the day off, and
you're not on shift either, right?
俺バイト休みだし、
ちーちゃんもシフト入ってなかったよね？
Chiho, are you working today?
千穂、あんた今日バイト？
Huh? Uh, no! Today I,
um... have other stuff to do!
うん、今日はちょっとその
ほかの用事あって
You be careful, now.
あんたも気をつけなさいよ
A-A-A-About what?! What do you mean?!
ななななな、何が、何の方
This neighborhood's dangerous lately.
近所でいろいろ物騒だから
Oh, that.
あ～そっちか
What else would it be?
そっちってどっち
Nothing, never mind!
何でもない
Chiho!
千穂
Hey, Emi, don't you live close to
where that shooting happened?
ね、今朝ニュースでやってた
銃撃事件って
恵美ちの近くじゃない
I'm three train stops from there!
えずみず離れているよ
Oh, huh. So, what are you doing for lunch?
そう、ってさ、お昼どうする
Wanna finally go to that curry place?
今日こそこの間言ってたカレー屋行く
I should warn you, there might be a line.
成らばないとダメかなだけど
Sorry, I don't have time to stand in line today.
ごめん、今日行列並ぶ時間ないの
I lost my wallet.
財布落としちゃって
What? For real?!
え、マジで？
Now I have to fill out
a bunch of forms on my break.
昼休みにいろいろ手続きしなきゃいけなくでさあ
Thank you for your call. This is Emi Yusa.
Thank you for your calling
This is恵美遊佐
"Yusa"? Sounds like you're a regular
Japanese already... Emilia the Hero.
遊佐？もはや完全日本に溶け込んだようたね
勇者エミリヤ
May I ask who's calling?
どちら様でしょうか
Someone who knows about
the hero and the Devil.
勇者と魔王知るものだよ
Someone with a plot to destroy you both.
そして、お前達を共に滅する類持つものさ
In which case, your repeated
access attempts last night...
そしますと
昨夜遅くのさいさんに渡るアクセスは
I certainly didn't expect you and
the Devil to form a united front.
勇者と魔王が共同戦線をはると予想外だった
I assure you that was not
our company's desired result.
当方としては大変不本意な結果です
I imagine not.
まあ、そうだもんね
Either way, the extermination of
King Satan and Emilia the hero
いずれにせよ、異世界に渡った魔王サタン
並びに勇者エミリヤも殺
is Ente Isla's collective will.
これはエンテイスラの意志だ
Excuse me?!
何ですって
I-I'm afraid I won't have an answer
until we investigate the situation.
こちらでも現況検討しなければ
お答えしかねますが
The situation that the hero and
the Devil fled from a little gunfire?
勇者を魔王守れてる襲撃
逃げ出し現況をどう検討するつもりか
How do you plan to investigate that?
I'm quite interested.
非常に興味深いね
This vile tone that seems to
echo from the pits of darkness...
この闇のさくから轟く卑しい響き
He's a demon.
魔の物だ
Alciel is the only great general left alive.
アルシエル以外に生き残りの四天王がいなかったはずね
Who in the demon realm are you?
貴方は魔界のどちら様
Perhaps you think you can scare me
with the words "Ente Isla's will,"
エンテイスラの意志などと言って
私を動揺させるつもりでしょうか
but I don't listen to those from your realm.
私は魔界の声などに耳を傾けない
I see. It's a shame you don't believe me.
そうか、信じてもらえなくて残念だよ
Talk to you again soon.
いずれ近いうちね
It takes all kinds, huh?
いろいろんな人がいるのね
Let's do lunch first. I'm sure the
banks are crowded right now anyway.
先にお昼済ませちゃおう
どうせこの時間銀行込んでるし
Hello?
もしもし
Hello, have I reached the
cell phone of Miss Emi Yusa?
もしもし、こちらは遊佐恵美さんの携帯電話でしょうか
Yes, that's right...
はい、そうですが
I'm calling from the Yoyogi Police Station.
私は代々木警察署のものですが
Huh?
は？
Police?!
警察
I never thought they'd ID us from that bike...
まさか、自転車からうちを割り出しとはな
Japanese police are pretty good.
やるの、日本の警察
Still, we were right about
the hero fudging her age.
しかし、予想通りでしたね
勇者の年齢をサバ呼んでたのは
As I recall, she's really
about seventeen or eighteen.
実年齢は確か十七くらいだったはず
Told you she must've
registered as at least twenty.
言った通りだろう
絶対二十歳以上で戸籍登録してると思ってた
Don't people usually fudge downward, though?
サバって舌に鯖読むじゃえいの（鯖読む　谎报）
My question is, why is the expression "fudge"?
そもそも何でサバ何でしょうね
Who cares about that?!
黙ってもいいよ、そんなこと
Why... Why... Why do I...
何で、何で、何で私が
Why do I, a hero, have to
be the demons' guarantor?!
何で勇者たる私が魔王いっばの保障人ならなきゃいけないよ
Wh-What were we supposed to do?
We couldn't think of anybody else.
しかたないだろう
ほかに思いやたなっかたんだから
It's not as though we wanted to ask
for your help with a thing like this.
こっちらだって本当はこんなことで
貴様を頼りたくはなかった
Well, I never thought I'd have to
use my seal and ID card for this!
私だってこんなことために印鑑で
身分署名証使うとは思わなかったわよ
I guess I could've asked my boss, but...
バイト先の店長に頼むってもあったんだが
We mustn't cause her trouble.
迷惑はかけられませんしね
But it's okay to cause me trouble?!
私ならいいっての
Well, duh. Causing heroes trouble
is the whole point of devils, right?
そりゃお前
魔王ってのは勇者に迷惑かけってものだろう
Does that make choosing me logical?!
だからって普通私は指名する
Aw, come on, we let you stay over last night.
いいじゃ、気のとめてやったんじゃん
Calm down, Emilia.
That's pathetic behavior in a hero.
落ち着け、エミリヤ
勇者ともあろうものが情けない
I'm not takin' that from you, Alciel!
貴方に言われたくないわ、アルシエル
Your fridge was empty! Put a little more
thought into your grocery shopping!
やらす缶の冷蔵庫もっと
計画的に買い物しなさいよ
"Most resourceful general in
the demon army" my butt!
魔王軍の一のしょうが聞いて呆れるわ
But it's... it's not my fault!
私のせいじゃ
私のせいじゃないのに
Listen up: I just got a threatening call at work.
いい、先、私の仕事場に
脅迫電話が来たわ
And they're after you, too, King Satan.
狙われるのは魔王
貴方も同様よ
What?
何だって
There, I warned you.
But I'll be the one to defeat you.
警告はしたわ
でも、貴方を倒すのは勇者である
こんな私よ
And don't you forget it!
忘れないことね
Don't you forget we're in public.
お前も公衆の面前だって忘れるな
A-Anyway! You just be careful not to get killed
by some nobody before you're defeated by me!
とにかく、私に倒される前に
どこぞ生まれ奉納にに殺されないよ
気をつけることね
They're after me and her both?
俺とアイツ両方狙っている
And they called on the phone, of all things...
しかも、電話をかけてきた
It's not my fault...
私のせいじゃないのに
しっかりしろう
- Get a grip. It's time to go home.
- My budget is perfect...
帰るぞ
I gotta meet Chi later.
この後ちーちやんと約束があるんだから
I'm home!
ただいま
Okay!
よし
Now, Sire,
して、魔王様、この佐々木さんとはどこで何時に待ち合わせて
where and when are you meeting
Miss Sasaki, and when will you be home?
何時にお帰りですか
What are you, my old lady?
お前は俺のおふくろか
We're meeting at five, at the
east exit of Shinjuku Station.
五時の新宿の東口だよ
We have some time, then.
All right, Sire, let us go.
まだ時間がありますね
でも、魔王様、行きましょう
Huh? Go where?
あ？どこに
Yes, this will do nicely.
これはなかなか
Where did the money for this even come from?
って言うか、こんな服買う金どこにあったんだよ
Naturally I've prepared a secret stash
for just this sort of emergency.
この世な一大事時のために手即利ぐらいは
用意してあります
"Emergency"? All I'm gonna do is drink
some tea, hear her out, and come home!
一大事だよ
約束って言ってもお茶して話聞いてさよならだぞ
This isn't necess...
別にこんな
You jest!
何おしゃいます
A teenage girl never tells her true
fears to anyone but close friends!
年頃の女の子の深刻な悩みを気心しれた
友達以外には絶対話しません
Not even her parents!
両親もです
Yet she told you, Sire!
それなのに、魔王様に話した
Surely you are wise enough
to know what that means!
その意味が分からない魔王様じゃありませんよね
I-I know. Yes.
わ、分かります、はい
Not to mention...
それに全身UNISLOのままでデートに行かせるわけにはいきません
I cannot allow you to go on a date
wearing Unislo from head to toe.
Y-You little...
お、お前
Apologize to the world's #1
apparel chain and to me for that!
アパルル業界No.1のUNISLOお礼に謝れ
ま、真奥さん
Mr. Maou!
Hmm? Chi, is that a new haircut?
あれ、ちーちゃん、髪切った
You noticed? I went for a
shorter style! What do you think?!
わかります、短くしてみました
どうですか
Looks pretty good on you.
お、似合ってるじゃ
Score!
やった
You look good, too. I thought
maybe you only wore Unislo!
真奥さんもUNISLOのばかり着てるのかと思いましたけど
Oh, no, not that there's anything
wrong with Unislo! Unislo is fine!
いやいやいやいやいや
UNISLOが悪いじゃないですよ
UNISLOもいいんですけどね
You just look... cooler than usual today.
今日はいつもよりかっこいいですね
Yeah, my roommate told me
I couldn't wear Unislo on dates.
同居のやつがデートに許しはなしって言うか
Th-Then you think of this as a date?
デ、デートだと思ってくれてるんですか
Huh? Uh, I guess?
あ、そう、な
Score!
やった
So, what should we do?
で、どうする
Let's go to Café Dotour!
カフェーとdoutorへ行きましょう
It's cheap, and it's pretty relaxing.
安いし、そこそこ落ち着けているんですよ
It's okay! Since you're giving me
advice today, it's all my treat!
大丈夫です、今日は相談に乗ってもらうですから
私が全部おごります
Hey, I'm an adult. I can treat
you to that much, no prob.
大人の面な
それぐらいおごるのは何でもねって
So, shall we?
それじゃ、行こうか
Um, M-Mr. Maou...
あ、真奥さん
Um... well...
あの、ええと
What? What's wrong?
何、どうしたの
Can I... hold your hand?
手、繋いでいいですか
That's all? Sure, I don't mind.
そのことか
いいよ、別に
- What's the matter?
- Hmm?
どうした
あ、いいえ、何でもないです
O-Oh, no, it's nothing!
Thank you!
ありがとうございます
We'll get split up if we don't hold
hands, anyway. It's super-crowded.
こうしないと逸れてしまっちゃな
人も多すぎし
Definitely. Somehow I just knew.
ですよね
何か分かっていますか
What are you lurking here for?
こんなとこで何してんのよ
Emilia!
エミリア？
Don't use my real name!
本名で呼ばないで
And more to the point,
you're acting blatantly suspicious.
というか　今のあなたはあからさまに怪しいわよ
Are you tailing someone?
誰か尾行でもしてるの
I-It's none of your business!
貴様には関係あるまい
I'm a hero.
勇者たる私が
Do you think I'll just let it go
when I catch you acting suspicious?
あなたたちの怪しい行動を見つけて
放置しておくと思う？
No, but please, just this once... for my sake.
思わんが
ここは私の代わり免じて？
For yoursake? I knew you
when you were a demon.
あなたの悪魔時代の顔を知ってる私に
何を免じるっての
Hey!
こら！
I'm so sorry, Sire!
魔王様申し訳ございません
- Alci... Ashiya! What are you
planning to do to that girl, you scum?!
アルジアシア！！
あの子一体何をするつもりなのか！この下種！
- You misunderstand!
- Alci... Ashiya! What are you
planning to do to that girl, you scum?!
誤解だ
His Majesty has no wicked intentions here!
魔王様は決して邪な考えが圧してるわけだ
Like a Devil can have non- wicked ones!
邪じゃない魔王がたまるもんですか
I'm begging you, listen to me!
頼むから話を聞いてくれ
So that's how it is.
そういうわけね
So you understand now?
分かってくれたか
My longtime foe is in a shameful
state, I understand that much.
私はの宿敵が非常に情けない状態に陥ってるだけが分かってわ
But why do they need to go on a date?
でも　何でデートする必要があるの
I wondered the same thing.
But after observing her,
私もそう思った
だが様子を見るに
it's clear that this "Sasaki" girl
is more than a little fond of him.
あの佐々木という少女は
魔王様に少なからず恋を抱いているらしい
I imagine so.
でしょうね
That doesn't bother you at all?
うん？そこはなんとも思わないのか
You want it to?
ご不満？
No...
いや　人間の少女ごときが
I just feel it's insolent in the extreme
魔王様に恋慕するのとは
for a mere human girl to
be enamored of my king...
不参もはなはだしいと私は思っているだけで
Personally, I wonder why a cute girl like that
私は逆に　何であんな可愛い子が
would be interested in
a good-for-nothing like him.
魔王ごとき改称なしにって思ってるね
You insult His Majesty?!
魔王様を侮辱するか
I am a hero.
勇者ですから
At any rate, right now any girl
who took one look at her could tell.
とにかく
あれ見てあの状況が分からない女はいないわよ
That trendy summer dress, plus it
looks like she was just at the salon.
この夏流行のワンピに
髪も美容院へ行ったばかりって感じ
What's more, those are new shoes.
それに靴も新品
What? They are?
何？そうなのか？
Men can't tell these things, I suppose.
男の人にはわからないでしょうね
She's using that material to evoke
the freshness of early summer,
素材で初夏の爽やかさを出して
フィット感でボディーラインを強調する
and the form-fitting cut to emphasize
her curv... Whoa, those are big.
っつ大きいよね
What are?
何事？
N-Never you mind! It's not like
big ones are useful in battle,
なん。。。なんでもないわよ
大きいことで戦いで役に立つことなんかないし
and small ones mean your plate armor is cheaper,
小さいほうが鎧の万鈞とかも安く作れるし
and they don't get in the way, either!
動くの邪魔じゃないし
- What are you talking about?
- Never you mind.
何の話だ
なんでもないわよ
Okay, so? Think you can get
anything useful from her?
で　どうなのよ
あの子の話から　何かえられそうなの？
Don't ask me.
知るか
I'm just following them to check
that no shady characters are around.
私は後で不信なやつかいないかチェックしてるだけだ
You're the shadiest one right now.
目下あなたが一番不信者
Still, this earthquake thing bothers me.
それにしても
あの子の自身の話　気になるわね
If what's going on with her
is connected to our world...
もしあの子の状況は私立ちの世界と関係あるとしたら
There's no point in spying
on them from here! Let's go.
こんなとこで見張ってたって何の意味もないわ
行くわよ
Go where?
行くってどこに？
That café, obviously!
決まってるでしょう
What?!
二人のいるカフェ
何だぞ　そんな大胆なこと
How could I ever excuse such audacity to His...
後で魔王様になんと申し訳。。おい！
Hey! Stop!
ちょっと待って！！！
で　詳しい話をもう一度聞きたいんだけど
あ。。はい
So, could you give me the details one more time?
マグドナルドのバイトは始めたぐらいから
耳鳴りがひどくなったって話はしましたよね
All right. I told you that
my tinnitus got really bad
最初はなれないことをやって
around the time I started
working at MgRonald's, right?
疲れてたと思ってたんです
At first, I thought I was just tired
from doing work I wasn't used to.
でもゆうべ
啊— 能听见么
But last night...
能听见么
もしもし？
Hello, can anybody hear me?
现在能听见么
もしもし
不行么
Can anybody hear me?
听不见~么 果然
Hello?
嘛 好吧
聞こえてますよ
No good, huh. I guess they can't hear me.
因为能够接通电话的家伙
很有限
I-I can hear you!
Oh, well. Not too many
people have the reception for it.
那边的世界应该发生异动了
What's going on?
最近有很大的异动
I'm sure disturbances are
happening in your world right now.
でかいなんて
可能是因为生气了吧 要小心了
瞅准时机
A big one might be coming soon, so watch out.
去一趟那边吧
A "big one"?
I'll come when the time is right.
聴いたことない言葉なのに
意味も分かるし
わけが分からなくて
I could understand him even though
I'd never heard his language before.
で　頻発してる自然現象ってことは
地震しかない考えたわけだ
I'm so confused...
So you figured he must mean the quakes,
since they're the main "disturbances" lately.
はい
間違いない
異世界の人間同士の意識は同調させ
Yes.
概念を共有する更新技術
No doubt about it...
That was the communication method
where humans in different worlds
イディアリンクだ
それを？？ディオーするさえ用いる短信技術
tune their minds in to each other
and share concepts... The idea link.
すなわちソナーをも放つ
They use sonar probe technology to do it.
はなだれたソナーは行った先で魔力の爆発を動くし
When the sonar pulse reaches its target,
it causes a magical explosion,
さまざまな現象となって現れる
今回の場合
地震という形に変わったことが十分考えられる
manifesting itself in various phenomena.
It's perfectly possible that the pulses
became earthquakes in this case.
最近俺たちの近辺で多発してるのは
ソナーが俺たちはエミリャ行路を追って
The fact that so many have
happened near us makes sense
はなたりとかたすれば展開いく
if we posit that someone's using
sonar to trace our and Emilia's route.
近いうちにでかいのが起こるか
これは思ったりも速くことが起こるぞ
A big one is coming soon, eh?
大丈夫ですか
どうしたんですか
Looks like things are gonna
happen faster than I expected...
なぜだ
なぜエミがアシアを一緒にこの店に入ってくる
Are you okay?! What happened?!
真奥さん？
Why?
大丈夫　俺何も悪いことしていない
Why is Emi walking into
this café, and with Ashiya?!
はい？
Mr. Maou?
ご免ご免
It's okay. I'm not doing anything wrong!
とにかくだ　千ちゃんの話を総合すると
Huh?
耳鳴りや変なことはさほど問題じゃない
Sorry about that!
So, to summarize, the tinnitus and
weird voices aren't really an issue.
感じなのは本当にでかいのが起こるかいながら
いざというとき
The important thing is whether
a big one is really coming!
自分の周りの人に
注意を流せるだけでも
だいぶ違うと思うよ
If so, I think just being able to warn the
people around you will make a big difference!
やっぱり真奥さんに相談してよかった
少しも胸の遣いが取れました
I'm so glad I asked you. It took some
of the weight off my shoulders.
どうだ意味？？
俺は何も悪いことしちゃいない
どう見ても立派な先輩アドバイスだ
Hear that, Emi?! I'm not doing anything wrong!
友達にも親にも
Anyone can see I'm being
the perfect senior part-timer!
誰にもいえなくて
でも真奥さんなら
I couldn't tell my friends
or my parents about it...
信じてくれるかもって思って
真奥さんやさしいし
But I thought you might believe me, Mr. Maou.
それにその。。
You're kind... And, um...
真奥さん　その。。。
私
M-Mr. Maou, um... I...
真奥さんが
やめなさい
この男に関わると碌なことにならないわ
I-I like...
エ、エミ？
Stop right there!
この男は見た目どおりの男ではない
No good can come of associating with him.
本性は狡猾で残忍よ
E-Emi!
This man isn't what he seems.
いきなりでなんて　ひどいことを言わないでください
His true nature is cunning and cruel.
おおおお姉さんは　真奥さんのなんなんのですか
D-D-D-Don't just pop out of
nowhere and say mean things like that!
私はこの男の敵
Wh-Wh-What are you to him?!
それ以上でもそれ以下でもないわ
こいつと関わると不幸になるわよ
I'm his enemy. Nothing more, nothing less.
おいエミやめろう
私に指示しないで
Bad things will happen to you
if you get involved with him.
千ちゃんもちょっと落ち着いて
Hey, Emi, cut it out!
真奥さん黙っててください
Do not order me around.
あ　思い出した
You calm down, too, Chi...
お姉さんこの前内の店に来ましたよね
You be quiet, Mr. Maou!
それが何
Now I remember. You came to our
restaurant the other day, didn't you?
もしかして　真奥さんのモトカノですか
So what?
何を言い出すの
Are you his ex?
やっぱりそうなんですね
なら　私が真奥さんにどうアプローチしようと
Where did that come from?!
Y-You are, then!
いまさらお姉さんと関係ないじゃないですか
In that case, however I come at him,
it's none of your business anymore!
馬鹿なこと言わないでもらえる？
私とこいつはそんな関係じゃないわ
じゃあ　何でいつも真奥さんの近くを
Would you stop talking crazy?
We don't have that kind of relationship!
うろうろしてるんですか
こいつと私の関係は
Then why are you always hanging around him?
簡単に語れるような間柄じゃないの
自分のほうが真奥さんと親密だと言いたいですか
What lies between us can't be
explained in just a few words!
どうしたらそうたれんなよ
Are you trying to say you're
closer to him than I am?!
さあ　とりあげがありません
だから二人とも落ち着いて
Where did you get that interpretation?!
It's the only possible interpretation!
Please, both of you, calm down...
地震だ
大きいぞ
- It's an earthquake!
- A huge one!
真奥さん
Mr. Maou!
どうなったの
よかった　気がついてのね
あなたは
What happened?
参ったわね　完全に閉じ込められたわ
Oh, good, you're awake.
You're...
真奥さんは？
Blech, we're completely trapped.
少なくとも私たちのそばにはいないわ
いえ　そうじゃなくて
Where's Mr. Maou?
Not with us, I can tell you that much.
あ　瓦礫につぶされちゃったんじゃないかってこと？
That's not what I...
そうね　ここであいつが死んででくれると喜ぶ人が
Oh, you're worried he got crushed by the rubble?
多いんだけどね
True, he'd make a lot of people
happy if he died today...
あいつは絶対に生きてる
あいつを倒すのは私なのよ
But I guarantee he's alive.
こんなところで死ぬなんて
I'll be the one to defeat him.
私は許さないわ
He's not allowed to die here!
そうですよね
きっと無事ですよね
ええ　きっと無事よ
Yes... I'm sure he's okay...
遊佐恵美わ
いっておくけど
Yep. He's okay.
真奥とは本当になんでもないだからね
I'm Emi Yusa.
And FYI, there's really nothing
between Maou and I, okay?
佐々木千穂です
今はそういうことにしておきます
で　真奥野？？どこに気に入っての？
I'm Chiho Sasaki.
I'll pretend to accept that for now.
なななな何を言ってるんですか？！
So, what made you fall for Maou?
魔王のこと好きだから私につっかかってきたんでしょう
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?!
スキって私　そんな
You picked a fight with me
because you like him, right?
L-L-Like?! No, I... I...
そんな簡単に分かっちゃいますか？
あだから見てれば誰でもわかるよ
Am I that obvious?
遊佐さんは　真奥さんのことを
Anybody watching you could figure it out.
どう思ってるんですか
私？
M-Miss Yusa, how do you feel about Mr. Maou?
真奥さんを敵だと言う割には
変にし親しいだったりしますよね
Me?
You seem really chummy with him,
for someone who calls him her enemy.
あいつって親しいなんて　絶対嫌なんだけどな
はい？
まあ知り合ってからずいぶんたつことが確かだけどね
Boy, would I hate to be his chum...
Huh?
でもあいつすきになったら
Well, it's true that we've known
each other for a long time.
つらい思いをするわよ
一応矯めたからね
But loving him will get you hurt.
何でかやく分かりませんけど
時期に分かる
Don't say I didn't warn you, okay?
いいえ　分からないほうがいいのかもね
I don't really understand...
You will.
とにかく　今は少しだけ眠ってて
Though actually, maybe it's better if you don't.
But for the moment... get a little sleep.
近くにいるんでしょう
千穂ちゃんは眠らせたわ
You're close by, aren't you?
I've put Chiho to sleep!
大きなお世話だ
魔王？！
そんな姿どうしたの？
I don't need you butting in!
しらん
なんかこうなってた
Maou?! What happened to your body?!
魔力が　戻っている
Beats me. It just sorta changed.
まったく　こん格好が
どうごまかせばいいのよな
His magic is back?
今なら
Man, I dunno how I'm supposed
to explain this to anyone...
今なら　最後の聖法気を振り絞れば
Right now...
こいつを倒すだけの聖剣を生み出すことができる
If I muster all the celestial
force I have left right now...
千ちゃんを頼む
I can still make a sacred sword
strong enough to defeat him!
ここから出るぞ
意外に被害は小さいみたいだから
Take care of Chi.
悠長に救助に待ってらないからな
Time to get out of here.
Looks like there are surprisingly few casualties,
俺が何とかするぞ
but we don't have time to wait around for rescue.
何とかする？
I'll find us a way.
よっしゅ　行くぞ
You'll find us a way?
どうしてよ
Okay, here we go...
どうして
魔王が人を助けるのに
Why?
Why... would the Devil save people?
一二三四
どこから朝になる
从何处开始是清晨
静かな空
安静的天空
Doko kara asa ni naru? Shizuka na sora
見ないふりをした指きり
装作没看见的拉钩
恋日の先笑われた
恋爱之前被嘲笑
Minai furi wo shita yubikiri koyubi no saki
つきなら  消えてゆくんだ
就算是月亮 也会要消失
Warawareta tsuki nara kiete
yuku n da kinou no houkaku e
昨日の方角
向着昨天的方向
うそつき　臆病者
胆小的人　说谎精
みんなまとめて　  僕なら　最低言ったのは
大家总结的这些　　我的话   就说声差劲
Usotsuki okubyoumono
minna matomete boku nara
夢の中だ
在梦中
Saite ita no wa yume no naka da
月の影に隠してた
藏在月影中
本当はね　泣いていだ
其实正在哭泣
Tsuki no kage ni kakushiteta
hontou wa ne naiteta
涙はもう流れない
眼泪已经不再流
枯れてしまうたな
枯竭了吧
Namida wa mou nagarenai karete shimatta no?
何もかも許せたら
虽然什么都原谅的话
流れるかもしれないけど
眼泪可能还是会流出来
Nani mo ka mo yurusetara
nagareru ka mo shirenai kedo
守りたいものばかりだなあ
全都是想要守护的东西
Mamoritai mono bakari da na
勇者、心の温かさに触れる
The Hero Experiences Human Warmth